Hello, I am Savita Maiti of ICC
Prudential Life Insurance
Company. I am an advisor [ __ ]
product trainer. Today I will
discuss pension plans with you. We know that
not everyone is an employee. It is not the case that
everyone who works will get a pension after retirement.
But yes, there is
nothing to worry about because ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance Company has
come up with various types of pension schemes that
can be your strength during old age.
Saving money is the only way to secure your future. Especially in
old age, this financial
security becomes very important and
that safety net has to be created.
From the very beginning of your career,
if you have
not yet planned any future plans or pension plans,
and if you want to secure your future now, then of
course, listen to the
matter that I will discuss today very
carefully and
call if necessary. The plan that I will discuss today
is
GPP. Here, a lump sum payment can be made.
This plan can be taken by paying a minimum of three lakh taka.
Here, two types of pension can be taken. Here,
you can take a monthly or annual pension. That is,
if you deposit money this month and
want to get a pension from the next month.  That is Immediate
Annuity and if you deposit money this month and
want to take pension after one year, two years or 10 years, then it is called
Department Annuity.
Therefore,
a lot more pension is available in this Department Annuity. This pension is of
two types. One is Joint Life
of ROP and Single Life of ROP.
Joint Life of ROP means that you will
get pension in your absence, the person you nominate will also
get pension in the same amount and the person you nominate will
get the entire amount you have deposited in his absence. Single Life means that
you will get pension for the rest of your
life and the person you nominate will
get the entire amount you have deposited in your absence.
In the case of Department Annuity, if you want to withdraw the entire amount two months before getting pension, even if there is
no interest rate in the bank post office in the future,
those who will continue to get pension in this GPP will get the same pension for life. In that case, there will be no
change.
I just discussed the pension plan, thank
you.